

# Miguel Lopes, Full Stack Developer

I have 8 years of experience building and designing software. Able to effectively self-manage independent projects, as well as collaborate in a team setting.

I love to work on web applications using technologies like Node, React, Tailwind, Next JS and GraphQL.

#### **Employment History**

# Web Developer at Miggs Web & Co., Houston, Texas

March 2022 — Present

Worked to assess competing websites in regards to content, look, and feel.

- Worked as a productive and positive team member to design, code, test, report, and debug operations.
- Effectively translated client requirements into application designs and system requirements.
- Remained knowledgeable in new standards, technologies, and trends in website development.

## Web Developer at Illusion Box, Barcelona, Spain

March 2017 — March 2022

Developed a application services platform as progressive with web app with React.

As part of the Front-end team, had exposure to tools like: Unit tests with Jest, design patterns and clean code.

I helped startups and other companies build apps, hired few juniors to work along side and execute several projects.

Helped an independent Electoral Institute to achieve they goals.

### Web Developer at Firmstep, London, UK

November 2015 — June 2016

- Worked as a productive and positive team member to design, code, test, report, and debug operations.
- Effectively translated client requirements into application designs and system requirements.
- Remained knowledgeable in new standards, technologies, and trends in website development.

#### Education

MCA, Computer and Information Sciences and Support Services, UOC, Barcelona

# BASc, Computer and Information Sciences, Leeds Metropolitan University, Leeds, UK

Skills	O HTML & CSS	0	JavaScript
	React	0	Git
	MysQL	0	Express.js
	MongoDB		
Links	Miggs Web & Co.		
Languages	English Native speaker	0	Spanish Native speaker
	Portuguese Native speaker		
Courses	Rice University Coding Boot Camp at Rice University		